Dmitrii Lisin

Software Programmer, Embedded Programmer

0035, Yerevan, Yerevan AM

☑ mrlisdim@gmail.com ☐ 8 (999) 529-5331

@mrlisdim (https://t.me/mrlisdim)

in dmitrii-lisin (https://www.linkedin.com/in/dmitrii-lisin/)



I began my career as an intern at an electronics design firm, I discovered that I enjoyed creating something that worked in real life rather than just inside my computer. I have finished a lot of embedded projects from different spheres and dealt with numerous instruments, protocols, and peripherals. It has always been my intention to write only high-quality, human-readable code. Had prior team leadership experience, but preferred to work as an equal member of the team. In my free time, I also prefer to extend my knowledge of programming languages, techniques, and trends by working with hobby projects.

SKILLS

Python Development Advanced

FastAPI | Pydantic | ORM | WAMP protocol | Async | Threading

CI/CD

Intermediate

Docker | Docker Compose | Github Actions | Gitlab Pipelines

Rust Beginner

Tauri

C++ Development

master

CMake | Make | STL | Concepts | C++17 | C++20

Web Development

Intermediate

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Typescript | React | Parcel | Rollup

Common

Git | Gitlab | Github | Reviewing | Linux | Reading schematics | Datasheet exploring

Embedded Development

Master

C/C++ | Zephyr | FreeRTOS | STM32 | Nordic | Real-time protocols | Industrial protocols | Stack only programming

Databases Intermediate

PostgreSQL | SQLAlchemy | PonyORM | SQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020 - Current

Team leader at LLC "Third Pin"

Developed a flexible testing system for embedded electronics based on distributed micro-services connected by PubSub/RPC Web-protocol.

- Robster: flexible testing system for electronic devices (Python, WAMP, Microservice, Docker, PostgreSQL)
- Gate valve controller (ARM, STM32, Zephyr, Modbus)
- GPS tracker for a professional training (ARM, Nordic, GPS, UBlox, Ant)

2013 - 2020

Embedded Software Developer at LLC "Third Pin"

Have been finished more than 20 commercial projects in embedded area including IoT, safety systems, shipbuilding.

- Pastilda: hardware password manager (STM32, ARM, Crypto Peripheral, SDIO, FatFS, FreeRTOS)
- Ship ruder control system (ARM, STM32, USB HID, FreeRTOS)
- Fire alarm system (ARM, STM32)
- MTUTA: Telemetry of vending machines (ARM, FreeRTOS, USB, SD, SIMCom, GSM, Ethernet, FTP)

PROJECTS

Pastilda

2016 - 2017

https://bitbucket.org/thirdpin_team/pastilda (https://bitbucket.org/thirdpin_team/pastilda)

Skills acquired: C++ | Embedded | Open-source

Open-source hardware designed to manage our credentials in handy and secure way.

Just Run My Debugger!

2021 - Current

Skills acquired: Rust | Rescript | Tauri | React

Pet project, simple GUI for OpenOCD debugger.

EDUCATION

Master Intelligent Technologies in Robotics at ITMO University

2016 - 2018

Bachelor Intelligent Technologies in Robotics at ITMO University

2012 - 2016

LANGUAGES

English Russian
Fluent Native Speaker

INTERESTS

Games Books Traveling

Hobby programming

Skills acquired: Typescript | Rust |

Rescript